{
    "target_configs": {
        "player": {
            "name": [
                "player_15_C6HKAY",
                "player_10_C6HKAY",
                "player_3_C6HKAY",
                "player_1_C6HKAY",
                "player_6_C6HKAY",
                "player_9_C6HKAY"
            ],
            "app_id": [
                15,
                10,
                3,
                1,
                6,
                9
            ],
            "animation": [
                "pick_up",
                "pick_up",
                "stand",
                "stand",
                "crouch",
                "liedown"
            ],
            "feature_caption": [
                "A bald man with medium skin, wearing a brown turtleneck, dark pants, and brown shoes.",
                "A man with medium skin, wearing sunglasses, maroon polo shirt, beige pants, brown shoes, and a watch",
                "A woman with medium skin, dark hair in a bun, wearing a dark V-neck shirt, light pants, and brown boots",
                "A man wearing sunglasses, dark green long-sleeve shirt, light cargo pants, black gloves, and brown boots",
                "A female soldier with light skin, wearing a black beanie, tactical vest, black shirt, pants, and boots, with a white scarf and communication gear.",
                "A man with medium skin tone, wearing a navy blue polo shirt, black pants, and blue shoes, with a dark watch on his wrist and black hair."
            ],
            "start_pos": [
                [
                    -1577.826,
                    -190.678,
                    98.275,
                    0.0,
                    -90.0,
                    0.0
                ],
                [
                    -1745.961,
                    -217.798,
                    98.15,
                    0.0,
                    -90.0,
                    0.0
                ],
                [
                    -2066.341,
                    -203.581,
                    98.15,
                    0,
                    157.1935761727804,
                    0
                ],
                [
                    -1895.79,
                    -203.692,
                    98.15,
                    0,
                    -175.48075124210925,
                    0
                ],
                [
                    -2027.245,
                    -331.349,
                    98.109,
                    0,
                    130.30909304905197,
                    0
                ],
                [
                    -1688.491,
                    -469.382,
                    98.15,
                    0,
                    99.02409705263244,
                    0
                ]
            ],
            "type": [
                "None",
                "None",
                "None",
                "None",
                "None",
                "None"
            ]
        }
    },
    "sample_configs": {
        "sample_center": [
            -1975.297,
            -1178.588,
            139.046
        ],
        "sample_radius": 1265.6555948133523
    },
    "refer_agents_category": [
        "player"
    ],
    "safe_start": [
        [
            -2014.949,
            -798.962,
            113.22,
            0,
            71.0966136586207,
            0
        ],
        [
            -1097.596,
            -282.325,
            98.15,
            0,
            178.9949795292304,
            0
        ],
        [
            -2507.57,
            -299.622,
            98.307,
            0,
            2.5664265216848494,
            0
        ]
    ],
    "Questions": {
        "relative_distance": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants, the_man_in_burgundy_polo_and_light_pants or the_woman_in_deep_V_top?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_man_in_burgundy_polo_and_light_pants",
                    "B. the_woman_in_deep_V_top"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_man_in_burgundy_polo_and_light_pants"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_man_in_burgundy_polo_and_light_pants, the_man_in_light_pants_and_sunglasses or the_woman_in_deep_V_top?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_man_in_light_pants_and_sunglasses",
                    "B. the_woman_in_deep_V_top"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_man_in_light_pants_and_sunglasses"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_woman_in_deep_V_top, the_woman_in_black_vest or the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_woman_in_black_vest",
                    "B. the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_woman_in_black_vest"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_man_in_light_pants_and_sunglasses, the_man_in_burgundy_polo_and_light_pants or the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_man_in_burgundy_polo_and_light_pants",
                    "B. the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_man_in_burgundy_polo_and_light_pants"
            },
            "Question 5": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_woman_in_black_vest, the_woman_in_deep_V_top or the_man_in_blue_polo?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_woman_in_deep_V_top",
                    "B. the_man_in_blue_polo"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_woman_in_deep_V_top"
            },
            "Question 6": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_man_in_blue_polo, the_man_in_burgundy_polo_and_light_pants or the_woman_in_deep_V_top?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_man_in_burgundy_polo_and_light_pants",
                    "B. the_woman_in_deep_V_top"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_man_in_burgundy_polo_and_light_pants"
            },
            "Question 7": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants, the_man_in_blue_polo or the_woman_in_black_vest?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_man_in_blue_polo",
                    "B. the_woman_in_black_vest"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_man_in_blue_polo"
            },
            "Question 8": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_man_in_burgundy_polo_and_light_pants, the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants or the_woman_in_black_vest?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants",
                    "B. the_woman_in_black_vest"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants"
            }
        },
        "counting": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "How many people are present on this suburban street?",
                "answer": "six"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "How many individuals are in a crouch position?",
                "answer": "one"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "How many people are standing up?",
                "answer": "four"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "How many men are wearing glasses or sunglasses?",
                "answer": "two"
            },
            "Question 5": {
                "question": "How many bald men are in the scene?",
                "answer": "one"
            },
            "Question 6": {
                "question": "How many women have a light skin color?",
                "answer": "two"
            },
            "Question 7": {
                "question": "How many men have a medium or black skin color?",
                "answer": "two"
            }
        },
        "state": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "What's the state of the bald man?",
                "options": [
                    "A. holding a bag",
                    "B. sitting",
                    "C. crouch",
                    "D. lying down"
                ],
                "answer": "A. holding a bag"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "What's the state of the man in the burgundy polo?",
                "options": [
                    "A. holding a bag",
                    "B. sitting",
                    "C. crouch",
                    "D. lying down"
                ],
                "answer": "A. holding a bag"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "What's the state of the woman in the deep V-top?",
                "options": [
                    "A. standing",
                    "B. crouch",
                    "C. holding something",
                    "D. lying down"
                ],
                "answer": "A. standing"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "What's the state of the man wearing sunglasses?",
                "options": [
                    "A. standing",
                    "B. crouch",
                    "C. holding something",
                    "D. lying down"
                ],
                "answer": "A. standing"
            },
            "Question 5": {
                "question": "What's the state of the woman in the black vest?",
                "options": [
                    "A. crouch",
                    "B. standing",
                    "C. holding something",
                    "D. lying down"
                ],
                "answer": "A. crouch"
            },
            "Question 6": {
                "question": "What's the state of the man in the blue polo?",
                "options": [
                    "A. lying down",
                    "B. standing",
                    "C. crouch",
                    "D. holding something"
                ],
                "answer": "A. lying down"
            }
        },
        "relative_location": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "Where is the man in blue polo relative to the bald man in brown sweater and black pants?",
                "options": [
                    "A. In front of",
                    "B. Behind",
                    "C. To the left of",
                    "D. To the right of"
                ],
                "answer": "A. In front of"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "Where is the bald man in brown sweater and black pants relative to the man in burgundy polo and light pants?",
                "options": [
                    "A. In front of",
                    "B. Behind",
                    "C. To the left of",
                    "D. To the right of"
                ],
                "answer": "D. To the right of"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "Where is the woman in black vest relative to the woman in deep V top?",
                "options": [
                    "A. In front of",
                    "B. Behind",
                    "C. To the left of",
                    "D. To the right of"
                ],
                "answer": "C. To the left of"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "Where is the woman in deep V top relative to the man in light pants and sunglasses?",
                "options": [
                    "A. In front of",
                    "B. Behind",
                    "C. To the left of",
                    "D. To the right of"
                ],
                "answer": "B. Behind"
            },
            "Question 5": {
                "question": "Where is the woman in deep V top relative to the woman in black vest?",
                "options": [
                    "A. In front of",
                    "B. Behind",
                    "C. To the left of",
                    "D. To the right of"
                ],
                "answer": "D. To the right of"
            },
            "Question 6": {
                "question": "Where is the man in burgundy polo and light pants relative to the bald man in brown sweater and black pants?",
                "options": [
                    "A. In front of",
                    "B. Behind",
                    "C. To the left of",
                    "D. To the right of"
                ],
                "answer": "C. To the left of"
            },
            "Question 7": {
                "question": "Where is the woman in black vest relative to the man in light pants and sunglasses?",
                "options": [
                    "A. In front of",
                    "B. To the back-left of",
                    "C. To the front-right of",
                    "D. Behind"
                ],
                "answer": "B. To the back-left of"
            },
            "Question 8": {
                "question": "Where is the man in light pants and sunglasses relative to the woman in black vest?",
                "options": [
                    "A. In front of",
                    "B. Behind",
                    "C. To the front-right of",
                    "D. To the back-left of"
                ],
                "answer": "C. To the front-right of"
            }
        }
    }
}